<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>course on assouline.sh</title>
    <link>https://assouline.sh/blog/tags/course/</link>
    <description>Recent content in course on assouline.sh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://assouline.sh/blog/tags/course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>College Graduation</title>
      <link>https://assouline.sh/blog/25-posts/graduation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://assouline.sh/blog/25-posts/graduation/</guid>
      <description>The day is finally here. I know this is what I&amp;rsquo;ve been working towards for four years, or more realistically, since like middle school, but it still doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel real. College graduations seemed to be this thing that happened to those older than me, and it didn&amp;rsquo;t really register that one year it would be my turn.
Since freshman year spring I&amp;rsquo;ve been making small blog posts here, and it&amp;rsquo;s insane to look back at where I started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux Malware</title>
      <link>https://assouline.sh/blog/25-posts/malware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://assouline.sh/blog/25-posts/malware/</guid>
      <description>My last semester, I wanted to take advantage of one of the last opportunities I may have to take a truly challenging class. We learned the basics of reverse engineering, and for the final project my group and I wrote our own malware- including the client and C2 server as well as the implant- to target an ARM-based Linux raspberry pi.
Our malware worked as follows:
Once our implant is successfully loaded onto our target, it calls out to our C2 over TLS to register itself and obtain an ID for future communications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CY3740: System Security</title>
      <link>https://assouline.sh/blog/23-posts/cy3740/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://assouline.sh/blog/23-posts/cy3740/</guid>
      <description>System Security (CY3740) was- and I anticipate always will remain- the best course I have taken at Northeastern. I strongly believe that every student in Khoury should take it, as no other class will push and engage you as much as this one. Professor Kaan gives students an extremely thorough, rigorous, and technical experience that ensures you fully understand the depth of the course material. All assignments were conducting real exploits against vulnerable systems, and submitting flags to prove victory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Udemy: Complete Ethical Hacking Course</title>
      <link>https://assouline.sh/blog/22-posts/udemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://assouline.sh/blog/22-posts/udemy/</guid>
      <description>Completed The Complete Ethical Hacking Course on Udemy.
This was a solid review of introductory cybersecurity topics and technical skills. While I didn&amp;rsquo;t learn many new concepts, I enjoyed coding the smaller projects alongside the course, like programming a MAC changer, network scanner, packet listener, and keylogger.
Here are some of the main topics covered:
Hacker Methodology Reconnaissance System Pentesting Network Pentesting Wireless Attacks Cross Site Scripting SQL injection </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS3500: Object Oriented Design</title>
      <link>https://assouline.sh/blog/22-posts/cs3500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://assouline.sh/blog/22-posts/cs3500/</guid>
      <description>Object-Oriented Design (CS3500) has been the most challenging course to date. The demanding assignments with extensive testing, coupled with the doubled pace of the course (since I took it over the summer) was quite stressful. However, all the late nights were well worth it, as I feel my comprehension of coding concepts and Java skills have developed tremendously. At first it was intimidating to have such free-reign about design and approach, but it grew my confidence in my technical abilities, and became my favorite aspect of the course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CY2550: Foundations of Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>https://assouline.sh/blog/22-posts/cy2550/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://assouline.sh/blog/22-posts/cy2550/</guid>
      <description>Foundations of Cybersecurity (CY2550) is the class I have been most excited about thus far. For once, instead of studying cybersecurity on my own and trying to navigate the mass of information out there, I would be given structure- a clear learning path. Though I didn’t learn a lot of new concepts, it was a great reinforcement of my previous knowledge. The genuinely fun assignments made me excited to continue progressing through my cybersecurity degree; I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to take more challenging cyber classes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EdX: Basic Network and Database Security</title>
      <link>https://assouline.sh/blog/22-posts/edx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://assouline.sh/blog/22-posts/edx/</guid>
      <description>Completed IBM&amp;rsquo;s course Basic Network and Database Security on EdX.
This was really exciting, as it&amp;rsquo;s the first cybersecurity related online course I&amp;rsquo;ve completed independently. It was hard to make time for it everyday- juggling college classes, clubs, and other responsibilities- but overall incredibly rewarding. I&amp;rsquo;d like to continue to fit independent study within my schedule.
Here are some of the main concepts covered:
Stateless inspection and stateful inspection OSI model layers Address Resolution Protocol (ARP) Intrusion detection system (IDS) and intrusion prevention system (IPS) Network address translation Ethernet and LAN-ethernet operations Transport control protocol (TCP) and user datagram protocol (UDP) Domain name system (DNS) and dynamic host configuration protocol (DHCP) Clustering and high availability systems Types of data and how to secure databases OS command injection and prevention tactics SQL injection and prevention tactics </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
